<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Scientist Portfolio on Nicol치s Cama침es</title>
    <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Scientist Portfolio on Nicol치s Cama침es</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 6: Signal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>This is the project carried out for the Signal Analysis subject in the Master&amp;rsquo;s in Data Science at the University of Valencia.&#xA;Through the completion of this project, the goal was to conduct research on the characteristics that can be extracted from musical audio signals and compare possible differences between different musical genres. The extraction of different features was done in Python using the Librosa library. This library is designed to facilitate the extraction of features from audio signals, as well as their manipulation and analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 5: Exploratory data analysis</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>This is the project carried out for the Exploratory Data Analysis course in the Data Science master&amp;rsquo;s program at the University of Valencia.&#xA;In this Exploratory Data Analysis project, a real dataset is explored to obtain valuable insights and conclusions. The dataset used for analysis belongs to the National Institute of Statistics (INE). Specifically, it is from a survey conducted on the population in the year 2021 with the purpose of providing detailed information about individuals, households, and buildings that cannot be obtained through administrative records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: Statistical analysis of the five major European football leagues</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>This is the project carried out for my final degree project for the Computational Mathematics degree at Jaime I University.&#xA;The project is based on the use of different data mining techniques, including principal component analysis to reduce the dimension of a data set, hypothesis testing to evaluate data, logistic regression to predict the occurrence of a binary event, and ordinal regression to predict categorical variables. The purpose of employing these techniques is to study data on various European football leagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Project Estimator and OpeanAI API Investigation</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>This project was carried out during my internship at the company Mas Ingenieros, while I was studying Computational Mathematics at the Jaime I University. The main objectives of this internship were the completion of two projects. The first involved researching and documenting the OpenAI API, and the second focused on creating a project estimator for internal use within the company.&#xA;The investigation and documentation of the OpenAI API began by thoroughly reading all available documentation on the OpenAI website regarding the functionality of their API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: MemWrist</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>This project was carried out as part of the Entrepreneurship course during my study period in the Computational Mathematics degree at Jaime I University. The main objective was to collaboratively develop a business plan with the rest of the team, centered around the idea of a product. Throughout the project, essential stages were undertaken, including product development, market analysis, competitor analysis, and the formulation of the business and financing model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Instagram Scraper</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>This project was carried out as part of the Computer Security course during my Computational Mathematics degree at the Jaime I University. The main objective of the project was to create an information extractor capable of gathering data from different profiles, as well as downloading posts.&#xA;The project methodology involved the development of a Python program. By using the Selenium Webdriver, Time, Os, Wget, and Warnings libraries, various functions were implemented to work in synergy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Since I completed my basic studies in high school, I have discovered my true passion for mathematics. It was this revelation that led me to choose the Computational Mathematics degree at the University Jaime I. Throughout my time at university, I explored various branches and applications of mathematics by engaging in different projects and assignments.&#xA;However, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until the period in which I combined my internship experience at Mas Ingenieros with the completion of my undergraduate thesis that I had a transformative encounter with my true professional motivation: Data Science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nicolascamanesantolin.github.io/Nicolas_Portfolio/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me through my LinkedIn profile or by filling out the following form.&#xA;Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
